(Raj:)Stuart's dressed like a
brother of the Night's Watch,
(Raj:)and they don't have sex.
(Howard:)There you go.
That's true.
(Sheldon:)Fair enough.
(Bernadette:)Hey.
You all right?
(Howard:)I'm fine.
(Howard:)Just a little embarrassed I had
to be carried down the stairs
(Howard:)like a baby.
(Stuart:)Thanks.
(Leonard:)Let's get out of here.
(Amy:)That was scary.
(Sheldon:)Well, the
important thing is
(Sheldon:)I said that big sandwich
would ruin everything,
(Sheldon:)and I was right.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Hey, Jon Snow!
(Raj(shouting from upstairs window):)How come your horse
has a basket on it?
(Stuart:)How come your head
has your face on it?
(Sheldon:)They don't wear bicycle helmets
in Game of Thrones.
(Sheldon:)You're thematically inaccurate,
(Sheldon:)but I applaud
your commitment to safety.
(Stuart:)Don't you guys have anything
better to do?
(Leonard:)Better than watching
a guy in a fur cloak
(Leonard:)ride a girl's
bike? Nope.